[
   {
      "id":1,
      "question":"Number(\"1\") - 1 == 0; \rWhat is the result?",
      "a":"True",
      "b":"False",
      "c":"NaN",
      "d":"TypeError",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":2,
      "question":"What is the result? \r(true + false) > 2 + true;",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"2"
   },
   {
      "id":3,
      "question":"What is the result?\r\"1\" - - \"1\";",
      "a":"0",
      "b":"2",
      "c":"11",
      "d":"\"11\"",
      "answer":"b"
   },
   {
      "id":4,
      "question":"What is the result? \r new String(\"This is a string\") instanceof String;        ",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":5,
      "question":"What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');        ",
      "a":"\"f,o,o\"",
      "b":"TypeError",
      "c":"[\"f\",\"o\",\"o\"]",
      "d":"[][][\"f\",\"o\",\"o\"]",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":6,
      "question":"What is the result? \r[] + [] + 'foo'.split('');",
      "a":"\"f, o, o\"",
      "b":"TypeError",
      "c":"[\"f\", \"o\", \"o\"]",
      "d":"[][][\"f\", \"o\", \"o\"]",
      "answer":"xxx"
   },
   {
      "id":7,
      "question":"What is the result? \rnew Array(5).toString();",
      "a":"\",,,,\"",
      "b":"[]",
      "c":"\"[]\"",
      "d":"(empty)",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":8,
      "question":"What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":1111,
      "question":"What is the result? \r\"This is a string\" instanceof String;",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"xxx"
   },
   {
      "id":1111,
      "question":"What is the result console.log(myArr); ? \rvar myArr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz']; \rmyArr.length = 0; \r myArr.push('bin');",
      "a":"['foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      "b":"['foo', 'bar', 'baz', 'bin']",
      "c":"['bin', 'foo', 'bar', 'baz']",
      "d":"['bin']",
      "answer":"d"
   },
   {
      "id":1111,
      "question":"What is the result? \rString('Hello') === 'Hello';",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":1111,
      "question":"What is the result? \r10 > 9 > 8 === true;",
      "a":"True",
      "b":"False",
      "c":"Error",
      "d":"Other",
      "answer":"b"
   },
   {
      "id":1111,
      "question":"What is the result? \rNaN === NaN;",
      "a":"true",
      "b":"false",
      "c":"TypeError",
      "d":"NaN",
      "answer":"b"
   }
]